[Music]
Hi everyone. In today's episode of
What's Cooking, we're going to have a
look at early access preview sandbox
environments. We have just released
version 27.0 of Business Central, but
you can already get a look at version
280.
I will go ahead and create a new
environment from Admin Center.
We currently support creating these
environments in USGB
and DE. I will select the type sandbox
and let's select the country DE.
I will select early access preview and
create. Make sure that you read the
information in the message box and that
you are aware of the preview terms
before confirming. So I will go ahead.
Here is an early access preview
environment that I created and it is on
version 28.0.
So I will go ahead and navigate to the
environment itself. And here is the
environment.
Now you will be able to explore and try
out all the latest Business Central
features before they are out on an
official version.
We display this notification bar to
remind you that this is an early access
preview environment and from here you
can also navigate to the documentation
page.
We are working on adding capabilities so
that you can easily discover new
features inside these environments and
provide feedback to us. Before I wrap
up, I wanted to mention a few things
that are important to know.
A partner sandbox license is required
for early access preview. We update
these environments to newer builds
weekly and these environments are not
meant to be used for production uh
because they may be deleted without
notice. And that is all I had. Thank you
so much for watching.